Guide to the Seattle Department of Community Development Housing and Neighborhood Development Central Files 1960-1979
Seattle Municipal Archives
Department of Community Development Housing and Neighborhood Development Central Files
1960-1979
City of Seattle Seattle Municipal Archives PO Box 94728 600 Fourth Avenue, Floor 3 Seattle, WA 98124-4728 Phone: 206/233-7807 Email: archives@seattle.gov http://www.seattle.gov/cityarchives
1620-02
Seattle (Wash.). Dept. of Community Development
18.0 cubic feet 21 boxes
Records documenting urban renewal and neighborhood development projects.
Historical Note
The Department of Community Development administered the City's comprehensive plan and provided direction and support for the City's physical and economic development through community planning. DCD was established in 1969 and assumed the responsibilities of the City Planning Commission and the Urban Renewal Program. In 1972, the Office of Economic Development was created in the Department to provide information to businesses that were expanding or relocating in Seattle. DCD was the lead agency for implementing various types of grant funded projects, such as Neighborhood Improvement Program, Targeted Neighborhood Assistance Program, and Neighborhood Development Program. DCD was abolished in 1992 and its programs were relocated in the Department of Neighborhoods, Department of Housing and Human Services, Planning Department, and other agencies. DCD records include material from the City Planning Commission, Zoning Commission, Metropolitan Arts Commission, Board of Adjustment, and Urban Renewal Program.
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, contracts, drawings, accounting records, and newspaper clippings relating to urban renewal, Neighborhood Improvement Projects, and Neighborhood Development Projects. Include records for Yesler-Atlantic, South Seattle, Northlake, South Park, Leschi, and North Greenwood projects. Early records in this series were generated by the Urban Renewal Program office.
Records are open to the public.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Seattle (Wash.). Dept. of Community Development; Seattle (Wash.). Urban Renewal Program
Seattle (Wash.)
Community development--Washington (State)--Seattle; Urban renewal--Washington (State)--Seattle; City planning--Washington (State)--Seattle; Housing--Washington (State)--Seattle; Pike Place Market (Seattle, Wash.); Yesler-Atlantic Neighborhood Improvement Project (Seattle, Wash.); South Seattle (Wash.)
City Planning; Seattle
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Department of Community Development Housing and Neighborhood Development Central Files, 1960-1979; 1620-02
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Seattle Housing Authority, 1976 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Community Profiles (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Contracts, General, 1974 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, General, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, Annual Report, 1976 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Policies and Procedures, Director of Off of Housing Development, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Policies and Procedures, Administration, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, Seattle Housing Authority, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Public Relations, Misc., 1977 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Press Release and Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Accountability Memoranda, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Affirmative Action Program, EEO, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Building Department, Inspection Services, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Building Department, Contracts, 1976 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Building Department, 1976 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, General, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Demolition and Site Clearance, 1975 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Engineering Department, Public Improvements, 1975 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, CETA, Real Estate Aide (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Policies and Procedures, Administration (Box-folder 1/20)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Policies and Procedures, Administration, 1973 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Press Release and Newspaper clippings, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Citizen Participation, General, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Budget, Re - Programming, 1977 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, General, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Physical Progress Reports, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Work Program Report, Quarterly Division Summary (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, Real Property and Acquisition Reports, 1973 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Physical Progress Reports, 1974 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Section 312, Chronological Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Housing Assistance Plan (Report), 1977 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Seattle Urban Renewal (Report), 1973 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, I - 90, 1976 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Housing, General, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Housing Assistance Payment Program, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Grants, 1976 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Environmental, General, 1976 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Northlake, Acquisition, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Northlake, Acquisition, Direct by the University of Washington, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - Northlake, Appraisals, Number One, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - Northlake, Appraisals, Number Two, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Northlake, Request for Concurrence, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Northlake, Consultants, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Northlake, Community Councils, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Northlake, Amendatory Application for Loan and Grant, Part One (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Northlake, Amendatory Application for Loan and Grant, Part Two (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Northlake, Amendatory Application (Second), Part One (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Northlake, Contract for Planning Advance (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Northlake, Loan and Capital Grant Contract (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Northlake, Amendatory Application (Second), Part Two (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Northlake, Amendatory Application (Third) (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Northlake, Time Extension (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Northlake, Amendatory Application (First) (Box-folder 3/11)
  - Northlake, Correspondence, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Northlake, Memoranda, Tenant Accounts, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Northlake, Environmental Impact Statement (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Northlake, Demolition and Site Clearance (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Northlake, Demolition Contract (Box-folder 3/16)
  - Northlake, Demolition Contract (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Northlake, Demolition Contract (Box-folder 3/18)
  - Northlake, Labor Standards, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 3/19)
  - Northlake, Fact Sheets, Statistics (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Northlake, Budgetary Status Reports (Box-folder 3/21)
  - Northlake, Capital Grant and Relocation (Box-folder 3/22)
  - Northlake, Claim for Relocation (Box-folder 3/23)
  - Northlake, Non-Cash Grants - in - Aid, 1974 (Box-folder 3/24)
  - Northlake, Non-Cash Grants - in - Aid, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/25)
  - Northlake, Non-Cash Grants - in - Aid, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Northlake, Preliminary Loan Notes, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Northlake, Project Loan Notes, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Northlake, Project Loan Notes, Second Series, 1974 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Northlake, Project Loan Notes, Fourth Series, 1974 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Northlake, Project Loan Notes, Third Series, 1972 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Northlake, Reports, Quarterly and Semi - Annual, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Northlake, Project Loan Notes, Second Series, 1971 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Northlake, Project Loan Notes, Third Series, 1970 (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Northlake, Survey and Planning Budgets, 1972 (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Northlake, Urgent Needs, 1976 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Northlake, Revised Application for Loan and Grant, 1963 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Northlake, Revised Application for Loan and Grant, 1963 (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Northlake, Tax Credits, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 4/14)
  - Northlake, Temporary Loan Notes, 1972 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Northlake, Proposed Third Sale, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - Northlake, Redevelopment, 1975 (Box-folder 4/17)
  - Northlake, Request for Concurrence in Disposition, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Northlake, Disposition Proceeds Estimates, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Northlake, Disposition, General, 1975 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - Northlake, Apostle verses City of Seattle, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Northlake, Apostle verses City of Seattle, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Northlake, Apostle verses City of Seattle, Final Decision, 1970 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - Northlake, Condemnation, 1972 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - Northlake, Land Purchase and Redevelopment Agreement, 1972 (Box-folder 4/25)
  - Northlake, Legal, General, 1972 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Northlake, Agreements and Resolutions, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Northlake, Wallingford and Montlake Community Council verses City, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Northlake, Shorelines Permit Appeal, Wallingford and Montlake, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Northlake, Organizations, 1971 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Northlake, Other Departments, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Northlake, Utilities, 1961-1972 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Northlake, Request for Certification of 112 Credit, 1965 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Northlake, Project Improvements, General, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Northlake, Northeast Pacific Street, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Northlake, Owner Participants, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Northlake, Property Owners, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Northlake, Public Hearings, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/13)
  - Northlake, Relocation and Property Management, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - Northlake, Relocation Study, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/15)
  - Northlake, Activity Reports, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/16)
  - Northlake, Liaison Committee, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/17)
  - Northlake, Owners, Landlords and Tenants, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/18)
  - Northlake, Liability Insurance, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/19)
  - Northlake, Physical Progress, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 5/20)
  - Northlake, Reports, General, 1974 (Box-folder 5/21)
  - Northlake, Special and Semi - Annual Reports, 1972 (Box-folder 5/22)
  - Northlake, Status of Land Acquisition, 1975 (Box-folder 5/23)
  - Northlake, Surveys, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 5/24)
  - Northlake, University of Washington, Wessman Report, 1968 (Box-folder 5/25)
  - Northlake, Report on Public Improvements, 1971 (Box-folder 5/26)
  - Northlake, Northlake Project, General, 1962 (Box-folder 5/27)
  - Northlake, Preliminary Design Report, 1965 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Northlake, Utilities Study (Box-folder 6/2)
  - South Seattle, Acquisition, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - South Seattle, Appraisers, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - South Seattle, Request for Concurrence, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - South Seattle, Consultants, General, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - South Seattle, Planning Advance, Contract for, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - South Seattle, Loan and Grant Contract, First and Second Amendment (Box-folder 6/8)
  - South Seattle, Third Amendatory Contract (Box-folder 6/9)
  - South Seattle, Fourth Amendatory Contract (Box-folder 6/10)
  - South Seattle, Correspondence, Loan and Grant and Amendatory (Box-folder 6/11)
  - South Seattle, Correspondence, General, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/12)
  - South Seattle, Memoranda, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/13)
  - South Seattle, Demolition and Site Clearance, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/14)
  - South Seattle, Fact Sheet, Statistics (Box-folder 6/15)
  - South Seattle, Cost Estimate and Finance Plan (Box-folder 6/16)
  - South Seattle, Financing, General, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - South Seattle, Relocation and Property Management, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 6/18)
  - South Seattle, Claim for Relocation Payment (Box-folder 6/19)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Part Two, Number Seven, 1965 (Box-folder 6/20)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Second Amendatory, Number Five, 1969 (Box-folder 6/21)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Fourth Amendatory, Number Eight, 1971 (Box-folder 6/22)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Second Amendatory, Number Two, 1969 (Box-folder 6/23)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Amendment Relocation, Number Six, 1968 (Box-folder 6/24)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Survey and Planning Application, 1962 (Box-folder 6/25)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Amendment Relocation, Number Four, 1969 (Box-folder 6/26)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Amendment Relocation, Number Six, 1969 (Box-folder 6/27)
  - South Seattle, Contract, Amendment Relocation, Number Eight, 1969 (Box-folder 6/28)
  - South Seattle, Non - Cash Grants - in - Aid, 1972 (Box-folder 6/29)
  - South Seattle, Non - Cash Grants - in - Aid, 1974 (Box-folder 6/30)
  - South Seattle, Project Note Sale, First Series, 1969 (Box-folder 6/31)
  - South Seattle, Project Note Sale, First Series, 1970 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - South Seattle, Project Note Sale, Sixth Series, 1970 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - South Seattle, Project Note Sale, Third Series, 1971 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - South Seattle, Project Note Sale, Fourth - Sixth Series, 1971 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - South Seattle, Request for Advance Payment, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - South Seattle, Request for Temporary Loan, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - South Seattle, Request for Temporary Loan, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - South Seattle, Request for Temporary Loan, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - South Seattle, Request for Capital Grant, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - South Seattle, Survey and Planning Budget, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - South Seattle, Tax Credits, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - South Seattle, Preliminary Loan, $3,290,000.00 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - South Seattle, Preliminary Loan, $3,875,000.00 (Box-folder 7/13)
  - South Seattle, Preliminary Loan, $3,800,000.00 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - South Seattle, Project Balance Sheet, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - South Seattle, Disposition, General (Box-folder 7/16)
  - South Seattle, Disposition, General (Box-folder 7/17)
  - South Seattle, Disposition, First Sale (Box-folder 7/18)
  - South Seattle, Disposition, Second Sale (Box-folder 7/19)
  - South Seattle, Land Marketing and Redevelopment, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - South Seattle, Disposition, Third Sale (Box-folder 7/21)
  - South Seattle, Real Estate Listing Agreements, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 7/22)
  - South Seattle, Condemnation, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 7/23)
  - South Seattle, Legal, Folder One, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 7/24)
  - South Seattle, Legal, General, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 7/25)
  - South Seattle, Maps (Box-folder 7/26)
  - South Seattle, Organizations, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - South Seattle, Other Departments, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - South Seattle, Plan, Urban Renewal, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - South Seattle, City, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - South Seattle, Landscaping (Box-folder 8/5)
  - South Seattle, Project Improvements, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - South Seattle, Utilities, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - South Seattle, Owners Participants, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - South Seattle, Property Owners, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - South Seattle, Public Hearing, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - South Seattle, Public Relations, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - South Seattle, Rehabilitation, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/12)
  - South Seattle, Owners, Landlords and Tenants Liability Insurance, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - South Seattle, Physical Progress, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - South Seattle, Special Reports, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - South Seattle, Status of Land Acquisition, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - South Seattle, Planning and Engineering Report (Box-folder 8/17)
  - South Seattle, Proposal for Economic Services (Box-folder 8/18)
  - South Seattle, Proposal for Planning and Engineering Services (Box-folder 8/19)
  - South Seattle, Reuse Appraisal Analysis (Box-folder 8/20)
  - South Seattle, Activity Reports, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Acquisition, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Land Acquisition Progress Report, Acquisition Number Two (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Appraisals, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Parcel Eleven -Three, Seattle Community College (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Proclaimers / Worksheets, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Request for Concurrence (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Parcel Forty -Three - One A (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Parcel Eight B, Seattle Koyasan Church (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Citizen Participation, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Committee, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Consultants, General, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Survey and Planning Application (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, First Amendatory Application (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Second Amendatory Application (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Contract for Advance Survey (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Loan and Grant Contract (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, First Amendatory Loan and Grant Contract (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Second Amendatory Loan and Grant Contract (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Loan and Grant Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Fourth Amendatory Loan and Grant Contract (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Fifth Amendatory Loan and Grant Contract (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Correspondence, General (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Correspondence, General (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Memoranda, General (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Memoranda, General (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Demolition and Site Clearance (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Environmental Impact Statement (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Fact Sheet (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Financing, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Non - Cash Grants - In - Aid (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Cost Estimates, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Loan Notes, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Note Sale, Sixth Series (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Note Sale, Second Series (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Note Sale, First Series (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Report on Budget Status, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Request for Advance Payments, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Tax Credit, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Temporary Loan Payments (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Temporary Loan Payments (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Temporary Loan Payments (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Temporary Loan Payments (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Temporary Loan Payments (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, General (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, General (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Maps (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Other Departments, General, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, Parcel Three (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, Parcels Five and Six (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, Parcel Twenty - Three A (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Yesler Atlantic Park (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Daycare Center (Parcel 26) (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, Parcel Twenty - Five (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, Parcel Thirty - Eight (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, Parcel Sixty - Eight A (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, Parcel Seventy - Eight (Box-folder 10/29)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Land Use, General, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 10/30)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, P-Patch, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Safeway Store (Box-folder 10/32)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Legal, General, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Parks, Playgrounds, and Schools, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 10/34)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Yesler Atlantic Park (Box-folder 10/35)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Parks, Playgrounds, and Schools, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 10/36)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Rezone Petitions (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Yesler Atlantic Park, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Urban Renewal Plan, General, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Improvements, General, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Improvements, General, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Urban Renewal Activities: History and Plan, 1975 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Public Relations, General, 1974 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Utilities, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Parks Department, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Gai's Bakery, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Gai's Bakery, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Property Owners, General, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Planning, General, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Improvements, General, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Improvements, General, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Pedestrian Pathway, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Pedestrian Pathway, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Property Owners and Owner Participants (includes agreements), 1972-1976 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Buddhist Church, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Randolph Carter Industrial Workshop, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Odessa Brown Clinic, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Bethel Christian Church, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Rehabilitation, General, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Rehabilitation, General, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Yesler / Atlantic Rehabilitation - Litigation, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Rehabilitation, Litigation (Bachman), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Public Hearings, General, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 11/26)